(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]||[]).push([[0],{10:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var n=r(0),s=r.n(n),i=r(3),o=r.n(i),a=(r(9),r(1)),c=[{id:1,questionText:"Consider two satellites S1 and S2 with periods of revolution 1 hr and 8 hr respectively revolving around a planet in circular orbits. The ratio of angular velocity of satellite S1 to the angular velocity of satellite S2 is",answerOptions:[{answerText:"8:1",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"1:8",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"2:1",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"1:4",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:2,questionText:"Ohm is a unit of measuring _________?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Resistance",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Voltage",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Current",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"None",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:3,questionText:"An object is executing uniform circular motion. Which of the following quantities remain(s) constant during the object\u2019s motion?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Velocity and Acceleration",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Speed and Velocity",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Speed and Acceleration",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Speed only",isCorrect:!0}]},{id:4,questionText:"With reference to the Sound waves, which among the following is / are correct statements? \n  1. The frequency determines the pitch of a sound, and the amplitude determines the intensity (or loudness)\n2. Frequency is proportional to amplitude \n\nSelect the correct option from the codes given below: ",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Only 1",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Only 2",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Both 1 and 2",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Neither 1 or 2",isCorrect:!0}]},{id:5,questionText:"What is dot product of two perpendicular vectors ?",answerOptions:[{answerText:1,isCorrect:!1},{answerText:0,isCorrect:!0},{answerText:-1,isCorrect:!1},{answerText:.5,isCorrect:!1}]},{id:6,questionText:"Which of the following provides potential energy to the object?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Its momentum",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Its position",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Its acceleration",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Its shape",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:7,questionText:"Which of the following is part of Classical Physics",answerOptions:[{answerText:"OPtics",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Thermodynamics",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Both A & B",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"None",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:8,questionText:"Who among the following Uncertainty Principle?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"R.A.Milkman",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Ernest Rutherford",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"S.N bose",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Werner Heisenberg",isCorrect:!0}]},{id:9,questionText:"Which of the following physical quantities has no units?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Pressure",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Relative Density",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Thrust",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Density",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:10,questionText:"Light year is a unit of which of these following?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Distance",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Speed",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Intensity of light",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Time",isCorrect:!1}]}];function l(){var e=Object(n.useState)(0),t=Object(a.a)(e,2),r=t[0],i=t[1],o=Object(n.useState)(0),l=Object(a.a)(o,2),u=l[0],w=l[1],T=function(e){e&&w(u+1);var t=r+1;t<c.length?i(t):p(!0)};console.log(u);var h=Object(n.useState)(!1),x=Object(a.a)(h,2),d=x[0],p=x[1];return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},d?s.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-section"},"You scored ",u," out of ",c.length,s.a.createElement("div",null,s.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return p(!1),w(0),void i(0)}},"Start Again"))):s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,s.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-section"},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-count"},s.a.createElement("span",null,"Question ",r+1),"/",c.length),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-text"},c[r].questionText)),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-section"},c[r].answerOptions.map((function(e,t){return s.a.createElement("button",{key:t,onClick:function(){return T(e.isCorrect)}},e.answerText)}))),s.a.createElement("div",null,s.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return T()}},"next"))))}o.a.render(s.a.createElement(s.a.StrictMode,null,s.a.createElement(l,null)),document.getElementById("root"))},4:function(e,t,r){e.exports=r(10)},9:function(e,t,r){}},[[4,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.7700d8b7.chunk.js.map